<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Launch X Journey Blog on My Software Development Journey Blog</title>
    <link>https://xanul.github.io/my_launchx_blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Launch X Journey Blog on My Software Development Journey Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xanul.github.io/my_launchx_blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Software Development Culture</title>
      <link>https://xanul.github.io/my_launchx_blog/posts/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xanul.github.io/my_launchx_blog/posts/intro/</guid>
      <description>In this first blogpost i want to talk about the software development culture and what it means to me to be a professional software developer, first I consider that being a good professional programmer implies a series of skills that must be combined to quality works and projects, some of the main skills and characteristics that I consider are important for a good software developer are:
 Willingness and desire to continue learning new technologies, concepts, and tools Tolerance to frustration and patience to solve problems in a calm and orderly manner Ability to be self-taught and learn by themselves, managing to find useful information about the current topic or subject, but always appreciating the knowledge from others Pleasure to work in a team, always prioritizing respect for others and having organization and willingness to advance and work as a team Passion and love for technology!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://xanul.github.io/my_launchx_blog/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xanul.github.io/my_launchx_blog/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>Who am I Hola, aquí vas a leer un poco sobre mi 🤩
 Excidit gente, si orat suo quaeque dura Calydon nata? Pars auro post stetit adfusique imis amplexus. Agmina per fabricator mittere Erymanthon habetque tot.
 Cineres Nile ipsa origine discurrunt adest Unde, et quem clausus, imo, virens quoque tales, potuit. Ingentes insilit corpore nutricis praebebat roganti licuit. Denique a vestros adulantum in bella lina parte et arte generi di igitur quis, digitis pedes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
